<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BettApplication</string>
    <string name="favorite_button_description">Favorite button</string>
    <string name="toolbar_favorite_button_title">Favorites</string>
    <string name="first_strategy_title">Sports betting on cup games</string>
    <string name="second_strategy_title"> Betting on late goals</string>
    <string name="third_strategy_title"> Betting on a draw</string>
    <string name="fourth_strategy_title">The Fibonacci betting system</string>
    <string name="fifth_strategy_title"> The Kelly formula</string>
    <string name="sixth_strategy_title"> Early cashout in sports betting</string>

    <string name="first_strategy_url"> http://gamesground.ru/uploads/posts/2021-05/1621847872_78956542.jpg </string>
    <string name="second_strategy_url"> https://photoshablon.com/foto_statji_6/705_1.jpg </string>
    <string name="third_strategy_url"> https://i.pinimg.com/736x/ef/da/79/efda79d3b757b9876cfb9d9a3dd2fc52.jpg</string>
    <string name="fourth_strategy_url"> https://www.bukbusters.pl/sites/default/files/tutorial-galeria/Ciag-fibonacciego.jpg</string>
    <string name="fifth_strategy_url"> https://vietradeportal.vn/phuong-phap-quan-ly-von-kelly/imager_1_40477_700.jpg</string>
    <string name="sixth_strategy_url"> https://i.gyazo.com/2cc391958779524f697c7076ff53b513.png</string>

    <string name="first_strategy_body">
        As a matter of principle,
        I don’t bet on cup games”; the above is often heard, but never really understood,
        because spectacular cup fights in particular offer so many opportunities for the sports bettor.
        It is not uncommon for David to meet Goliath. In relation to the big club, it is not rarely an annoying duty,
        but for the small club it is the undisputed game of the year.
        And thus, now and then, there is the chance to win good odds and value bets.
        It can be worthwhile to prepare more closely for cup games. In times of YouTube and dynamic club websites,
        it is in many cases not a problem to follow the press conference before the game;
        which players will be included in the squad for the game? Which regular players or even stars are spared?
        Is the second goalkeeper playing? Will young players get their chance?
        All of the above are interesting questions when looking for a lucrative bet.

        Of course, it always depends on the club’s approach – cup games are always a question of mentality.
        It is therefore a good idea to analyze the past few weeks.
        Does a larger club need to rehabilitate for weak games within the past weeks and maybe would like to let off steam on a “little one” in the cup? How cup-affine is a club in general?
        There are enough examples of quite large clubs that have suffered from a cup curse for years or even decades.
        Yes, in fact there is hardly any other even, where you there are more to analyze than in cup competitions.
        The advantage, however, is that there will be numerous bets that, on closer inspection, will pass as value bets.
        Even if the bookmakers, probably because they cannot plan and pre-analyze every game themselves,
        keep the odds lower in the cup and pay a lower commission.
    </string>
    <string name="second_strategy_body">  For example in relation to late goals betting,
        look for games with a clear favourite with 3-way winning odds of less than 1.30.
        In a betting round, spread the risk over as many games as possible;
        obviously, there will always be some unexpected losses.
        Then, bet on late goals for each of these games.
        Most bookmakers offer these bets under the name “Last goal will be in minutes 76-90”.
        Statistically, you will win just under 60% of all of these bets.  </string>

    <string name="third_strategy_body"> A tie is not the most popular bet out there.
        If only, because it is much more fun to celebrate a team’s victory.
        Another quick and easy way to identify potential ties is to check the Asian handicap odds.

        Look for games in which the handicap was set to zero (0) or a draw.
        This means that both teams have been rated more or less equally,
        and the bookmakers do not want to give either team a head start.
        Games like these tend to end in a draw more often than you might think.
    </string>

    <string name="fourth_strategy_body">The Fibonacci betting system is one of many betting strategies available today.
         Here we explain what it is all about.
         The Fibonacci betting strategy

         Fibonacci sequence betting is undoubtedly a controversial concept.
        But there are definitely sports bettors who were able to achieve great success with it.
        This strategy carries some risks, but with the necessary luck and the right nose, you can be successful while employing this strategy.

        The basic concept of betting according to the Fibonacci sequence is simple: bet on a tie.
        If you lose, just bet on the next tie according to a certain key and start increasing your stake. </string>

    <string name="fifth_strategy_body"> There are of course numerous ideas,
        concepts and formulas that can help you calculate the ideal stake on a bet. One of them is the Kelly formula.

        Of course, this is no guarantee that you will always bet correctly and the assessment of how likely the outcome of a game is,
        does still remain up to you.
        But the Kelly formula can help you choose the size of your bet.

        This is how the Kelly formula works

        You choose a game or an event and rate the outcome as a percentage
        Example: Austria defeats Germany – you rate this outcome with a probability of 20%
        Now, you are looking for an odd for this event that seems fair to you
        Then, you put the probability and the odds in the Kelly formula and get a value from it
        The Kelly Formula hereby recommends that, given the probability that you have determined yourself and the odds you have chosen,
        you should bet 2.22% of your bankroll on this event.
    </string>

    <string name="sixth_strategy_body">  Have you ever regretted placing a particular bet and wished that you could somehow withdraw it?
        Or maybe you had doubts as to whether the team you supported could really hold the lead?
        If your answer to any of the questions is yes, then you’ll love the early withdrawal option.
        These properties give the speculator more control over the bets already placed and could ultimately make a big difference in the overall bankroll if you wager your cards correctly.
        The early payout is often referred to as the cashout by most sports betting sites.

        What is the early withdrawal option?

        The early withdrawal option allows sports bettors to withdraw their bets early,
        before they have been settled. So, you can either make a profit or get a part of your stake back,
        depending on your selection at that time. The feature is available as soon as you have placed your pre-match
        or in-play bet and the payout amount will fluctuate based on the events taking place in the game.   </string>

</resources>